{
    "temperature_0.5": [
        {
            "question": "Can pig hearts be used for human transplants?",
            "answer": "Yes, pig hearts can be used for human transplants [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did the man receive a pig heart transplant?",
            "answer": "The man received a pig heart transplant because it was the only currently available option for him due to his terminal heart disease and his ineligibility for a conventional heart transplant or an artificial heart pump [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why is Elizabeth Holmes on trial?",
            "answer": "Elizabeth Holmes is on trial for charges of defrauding investors and patients [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Is Elizabeth Holmes guilty?",
            "answer": "Yes, Elizabeth Holmes is guilty. She was found guilty on four charges of defrauding investors [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the Supreme Court's ruling on the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers?",
            "answer": "The Supreme Court blocked the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/13/business/us-supreme-court-ruling-vaccine-mandate/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What companies took action against Russia?",
            "answer": "McDonald's, Starbucks, Coca-Cola, and PepsiCo took action against Russia [1]. Ford and General Motors also suspended their operations in Russia [2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/business/mcdonalds-pepsi-coke-russia/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the US's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "The US's stance on the Ukraine crisis is that it is wary of intervention and does not want to play a major role. Only 26% of Americans believe the US should play a major role, while 52% believe it should play a minor role and 20% believe it should play no role at all [1,2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/27/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-what-matters/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/24/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-nato/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What is China's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "China's stance on the Ukraine crisis is that it has refused to condemn the Russian attack or call it an \"invasion\" and has expressed understanding for Moscow's \"legitimate security concerns\" [1]. China has also stated that it does not want the sanctions against Russia to affect China and has refused to condemn Russia's attack on Ukraine [2]. However, China has called for a diplomatic resolution to the crisis and supports Russia and Ukraine resolving their issue through negotiation [3,4].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/07/asia/china-india-ukraine-reaction-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/17/business/china-russia-sanctions-friction-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/18/china/china-winter-olympics-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/china/china-reaction-ukraine-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Did the US send troops to Ukraine?",
            "answer": "The US did not send troops to Ukraine [1,2,3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/27/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-what-matters/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/24/europe/nato-deployment-eastern-europe-ukraine-intl/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/02/politics/president-authority-deploy-us-troops-explainer/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are companies are moving out of Russia?",
            "answer": "Companies are moving out of Russia in response to its invasion of Ukraine, which has led to an exodus of major corporations from various sectors of the economy. The reasons for their departure include concerns about the situation in Ukraine [1], the end of their presence in Russia after many years [2], the suspension of new development activity and future hotel investment [1], the halt of operations and reduced product offerings [1], and the expansion of exit processes to reduce operations and exposure in Russia [3]. The companies are likely responding to the political and economic implications of the invasion and the resulting sanctions imposed on Russia. [1,2,3]",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/oil-prices-natural-gas-russia/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/14/investing/citi-russia/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who's nominated for best supporting actress?",
            "answer": "The nominees for best supporting actress are Jessie Buckley, Ariana DeBose, Judi Dench, Kirsten Dunst, and Aunjanue Ellis [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/entertainment/oscar-nominations-list-2022/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Ketanji Jackson?",
            "answer": "Ketanji Jackson is a judge who has appeared before the Senate three times for confirmation proceedings for prior roles. She is currently serving on the DC US Circuit Court of Appeals [1]. She grew up in Miami and comes from a working-class family that valued education [2]. Her parents were in public service, her brother was a police officer and in the military, and she has uncles who served as police officers, one of whom became the police chief in Miami [3]. She has a husband who is a surgeon and they have two daughters [2]. She was nominated by President Joe Biden to be the first Black woman to sit on the Supreme Court [2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/21/politics/what-to-expect-ketanji-brown-jackson-confirmation-hearings/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/who-is-ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-scotus-nominee/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/supreme-court-ketanji-brown-jackson/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the controversy surrounding Eileen Gu",
            "answer": "The controversy surrounding Eileen Gu is that she was spotted not singing China's national anthem during the medal ceremony, which has led to increased public scrutiny [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Eileen Gu?",
            "answer": "Eileen Gu is a freestyle skier who was born in the United States to a Chinese mother and American father. She made the decision to compete for China instead of the US and has become a popular figure in China, known for her skiing abilities, fluent Mandarin, and familiarity with Chinese culture. She has a large following on social media platforms like Weibo and Xiaohongshu, and is often referred to as \"Miss Perfect\" by her fans. [1,2,3,4]",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/06/sport/us-born-figure-skater-beverly-zhu-yi-china-olympic-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/china/eileen-gu-wins-big-air-olympics-intl-hnk-spt/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/07/china/eileen-gu-olympics-foreign-athletes-mic-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What images did James Webb Telescope capture?",
            "answer": "The James Webb Space Telescope captured images of 18 points of starlight from the same star in each of its 18 mirror segments [1]. The telescope also captured images of individual galaxies and stars behind the star in the image [2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/world/james-webb-space-telescope-selfie-images-scn/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/16/world/james-webb-space-telescope-mirror-alignment-scn/index.html"
            }
        }
    ],
    "temperature_0.9": [
        {
            "question": "Can pig hearts be used for human transplants?",
            "answer": "Yes, pig hearts can be used for human transplants. [1]",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did the man receive a pig heart transplant?",
            "answer": "The man received a pig heart transplant because it was \"the only currently available option\" for his terminal heart disease [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why is Elizabeth Holmes on trial?",
            "answer": "Elizabeth Holmes is on trial for charges of defrauding investors [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Is Elizabeth Holmes guilty?",
            "answer": "Yes, Elizabeth Holmes is guilty [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the Supreme Court's ruling on the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers?",
            "answer": "The Supreme Court blocked the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/13/business/us-supreme-court-ruling-vaccine-mandate/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What companies took action against Russia?",
            "answer": "Companies that took action against Russia include BASF[1], BP[1], Coca-Cola HBC[1], Ford[2], General Motors[2], McDonald's[3], Starbucks[3], PepsiCo[3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/investing/business-russia-sanctions/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/business/mcdonalds-pepsi-coke-russia/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the US's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "The US's stance on the Ukraine crisis is not clearly stated in the given documents.",
            "reference": {}
        },
        {
            "question": "What is China's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "China's stance on the Ukraine crisis is that it has refused to condemn Russia's attack or call it an \"invasion,\" and has stated that it understands Moscow's \"legitimate security concerns\" [1]. China has also expressed support for state sovereignty and territorial integrity, emphasizing that there is only one China and that Taiwan is an inalienable part of China's territory [2]. Additionally, China has expressed a desire for a diplomatic resolution to the crisis and has called for negotiations between Russia and Ukraine [3,4]. China has not taken a position that contradicts its principle of respecting national sovereignty and territorial integrity [2]. However, it is important to note that China wants to avoid being impacted by the sanctions against Russia and has indicated that it does not want the crisis to affect China [5].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/07/asia/china-india-ukraine-reaction-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/23/china/taiwan-ukraine-parallels-china-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/18/china/china-winter-olympics-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/china/china-reaction-ukraine-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "5": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/17/business/china-russia-sanctions-friction-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Did the US send troops to Ukraine?",
            "answer": "The US did not send troops to Ukraine [1,2,3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/27/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-what-matters/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/24/europe/nato-deployment-eastern-europe-ukraine-intl/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/02/politics/president-authority-deploy-us-troops-explainer/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are companies are moving out of Russia?",
            "answer": "Companies are moving out of Russia in response to its invasion of Ukraine, which has led to an exodus of major corporations from various sectors of the economy [1]. The companies are concerned about the situation in Ukraine and have decided to suspend or scale back their operations in Russia [1]. The decision to leave Russia has been made by companies in the automotive industry, such as Ford and General Motors, as well as companies in the energy sector, including Exxon, BP, Shell, Equinor, and TotalEnergies [1,2]. Additionally, companies in the hospitality industry, such as Hilton and Marriott, have also shut down their corporate offices and suspended development activities in Russia [1]. Industrial companies like 3M and Dow have halted operations, reduced product offerings, and stopped investments in Russia [1]. Sanctions and concerns about moral or brand reputation have also been mentioned as potential factors influencing companies' decisions [3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/oil-prices-natural-gas-russia/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/12/europe/western-brands-russia-sanctions-impact-intl/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who's nominated for best supporting actress?",
            "answer": "The nominees for Best Supporting Actress are Jessie Buckley, Ariana DeBose, Judi Dench, Kirsten Dunst, and Aunjanue Ellis [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/entertainment/oscar-nominations-list-2022/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Ketanji Jackson?",
            "answer": "Ketanji Jackson is a judge who has served on the DC US Circuit Court of Appeals. She has appeared before the Senate three times for confirmation proceedings for prior roles and is currently facing a confirmation hearing for her Supreme Court nomination. She is a Harvard Law graduate and has a background in public service. Jackson is known for her qualifications, thoughtfulness, evenhandedness, and collegiality. She would be the first Black woman on the Supreme Court if confirmed [1]. She has a family background in public service, with her parents and uncle being involved in law enforcement and her brother being a police officer and military member [2]. She has also participated in speech and debate, winning a national championship, and has traveled extensively for tournaments [3]. Her husband is named Patrick Jackson and they have two daughters [3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/21/politics/what-to-expect-ketanji-brown-jackson-confirmation-hearings/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/supreme-court-ketanji-brown-jackson/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/who-is-ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-scotus-nominee/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the controversy surrounding Eileen Gu",
            "answer": "The controversy surrounding Eileen Gu revolves around her citizenship and her actions during the Olympic medal ceremony. She has repeatedly dodged questions about her citizenship, and during the medal ceremony, she was seen not singing China's national anthem when the Chinese flag was raised [1,2]. This has led to increased public scrutiny and criticism [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/18/sport/eileen-gu-halfpipe-gold-olympics-intl-hnk-spt/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Eileen Gu?",
            "answer": "Eileen Gu is an American-born freestyle skier who competes for China in the Beijing Winter Olympics. She has gained popularity in China and is viewed as a national darling. Gu speaks fluent Mandarin and has embraced her cultural heritage. She has a large following on social media platforms like Weibo and Xiaohongshu [1,2,3,4].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/06/sport/us-born-figure-skater-beverly-zhu-yi-china-olympic-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/china/eileen-gu-wins-big-air-olympics-intl-hnk-spt/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/07/china/eileen-gu-olympics-foreign-athletes-mic-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What images did James Webb Telescope capture?",
            "answer": "The James Webb Telescope captured images of 18 points of starlight reflected by its mirror segments [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/world/james-webb-space-telescope-selfie-images-scn/index.html"
            }
        }
    ],
    "temperature_0.1": [
        {
            "question": "Can pig hearts be used for human transplants?",
            "answer": "Yes, pig hearts can be used for human transplants [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did the man receive a pig heart transplant?",
            "answer": "The man received a pig heart transplant because it was the only currently available option for him due to his terminal heart disease and ineligibility for a conventional heart transplant or an artificial heart pump [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/10/health/genetically-modified-pig-heart-transplant/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why is Elizabeth Holmes on trial?",
            "answer": "Elizabeth Holmes is on trial for charges of defrauding investors and patients [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Is Elizabeth Holmes guilty?",
            "answer": "Yes, Elizabeth Holmes is guilty. She was found guilty on four charges of defrauding investors [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/03/tech/elizabeth-holmes-verdict/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the Supreme Court's ruling on the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers?",
            "answer": "The Supreme Court blocked the Biden administration's vaccine mandate for large employers [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/13/business/us-supreme-court-ruling-vaccine-mandate/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What companies took action against Russia?",
            "answer": "McDonald's, Starbucks, Coca-Cola, and PepsiCo took action against Russia [1]. Ford and General Motors also suspended their operations in Russia [2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/08/business/mcdonalds-pepsi-coke-russia/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the US's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "The US's stance on the Ukraine crisis is that it is wary of intervention and does not want to play a major role in the situation [1,2]. However, the US has not taken any options off the table and may consider targeting the Russian energy sector with sanctions [1]. The US is also committed to defending Ukraine and will respond severely if any type of incursion or interference takes place [3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/27/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-what-matters/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/24/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-nato/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/01/25/europe/dmytro-kuleba-ukraine-interview-clarissa-ward-intl/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What is China's stance on the Ukraine crisis?",
            "answer": "China's stance on the Ukraine crisis is that it has refused to condemn the Russian attack or call it an \"invasion\" and has said it understands Moscow's \"legitimate security concerns.\" China has also stated that it wants a diplomatic resolution to the crisis and supports Russia and Ukraine resolving their issue through negotiation. However, China has emphasized its principle of respecting national sovereignty and territorial integrity and has denied taking a position on Ukraine that contradicts this principle [1,2,3,4].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/07/asia/china-india-ukraine-reaction-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/23/china/taiwan-ukraine-parallels-china-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/18/china/china-winter-olympics-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/china/china-reaction-ukraine-russia-intl-hnk-mic/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Did the US send troops to Ukraine?",
            "answer": "No, the US did not send troops to Ukraine [1,2].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/27/politics/us-troops-ukraine-russia-what-matters/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/02/politics/president-authority-deploy-us-troops-explainer/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are companies are moving out of Russia?",
            "answer": "Companies are moving out of Russia in response to its invasion of Ukraine, which has led to an exodus of major corporations from various sectors of the economy [1]. The reasons for their departure include concerns about the situation in Ukraine [1], the hit to their balance sheets [2], and the impact of sanctions [3]. Additionally, companies like Ford and General Motors have expressed deep concern about the situation in Ukraine [1]. The closure of corporate offices, suspension of new development activities, and halting of operations and investments in Russia by companies like Hilton, Marriott, 3M, and Dow further indicate the scale of the exodus [1]. Citigroup, Goldman Sachs, JPMorgan, and Deutsche Bank have also announced their plans to exit or reduce their operations and exposure in Russia [4].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/companies-pulling-back-russia-ukraine-war-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/02/business/oil-prices-natural-gas-russia/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/12/europe/western-brands-russia-sanctions-impact-intl/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/14/investing/citi-russia/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who's nominated for best supporting actress?",
            "answer": "The nominees for Best Supporting Actress are Jessie Buckley, Ariana DeBose, Judi Dench, Kirsten Dunst, and Aunjanue Ellis [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/entertainment/oscar-nominations-list-2022/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Ketanji Jackson?",
            "answer": "Ketanji Jackson is a judge who has appeared before the Senate three times for confirmation proceedings for prior roles [1]. She is currently serving on the DC US Circuit Court of Appeals [1]. She has a background in public service and her family has a history of law enforcement [2]. She is the nominee for the Supreme Court and, if confirmed, will be the first Black woman on the Supreme Court [1]. She has a strong resume and professional diversity, including two stints at Harvard, prestigious clerkships, judicial opinions, forays into public service, and time served in Big Law [3]. She was previously nominated by President Obama to the US District Court for the District of Columbia [3].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/03/21/politics/what-to-expect-ketanji-brown-jackson-confirmation-hearings/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/supreme-court-ketanji-brown-jackson/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/25/politics/who-is-ketanji-brown-jackson-biden-scotus-nominee/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What's the controversy surrounding Eileen Gu",
            "answer": "The controversy surrounding Eileen Gu is that she was spotted not singing China's national anthem during the medal ceremony, which led to increased public scrutiny [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Eileen Gu?",
            "answer": "Eileen Gu is a freestyle skier who was born and raised in California. She has a Chinese mother and an American father. She gained popularity in China and is considered a national darling. She is known for her success in skiing, her fashion choices, and her fluency in Mandarin. She has a large following on social media platforms like Weibo and Xiaohongshu. She has become the unofficial face of the Winter Olympics in China and has been featured heavily in state media coverage and advertisements for Chinese brands [1,2,3,4].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/06/sport/us-born-figure-skater-beverly-zhu-yi-china-olympic-intl-hnk/index.html",
                "2": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/china/eileen-gu-zhu-yi-nathan-chen-comparison-intl-hnk-dst/index.html",
                "3": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/08/china/eileen-gu-wins-big-air-olympics-intl-hnk-spt/index.html",
                "4": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/07/china/eileen-gu-olympics-foreign-athletes-mic-intl-hnk/index.html"
            }
        },
        {
            "question": "What images did James Webb Telescope capture?",
            "answer": "The James Webb Space Telescope captured images of 18 points of starlight reflected by its mirror segments [1].",
            "reference": {
                "1": "https://www.cnn.com/2022/02/11/world/james-webb-space-telescope-selfie-images-scn/index.html"
            }
        }
    ]
}